Contact

5/1557, Sree Ram Nagar, Proddatur 9490450034 (Mobile) rajeshjanapati@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rajesh-kumarjanapati-564496194 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Workato

IoT data integration with iPaaS Tools using API Management

Python (Programming Language)

Certifications

Applied Gen AI in Workato
API Platform
Learn Industrial Automation
Automation Pro II Certification
Automation Pro I Certification

Rajesh Kumar Janapati

Sr. Software Engineer at Yucca Scalian Group (Yucca IT Solutions) | Workato Developer | Workato Certified | ChatBOT Design | IoT Developer | Internet Of Things |

Proddatur, Andhra Pradesh, India

Summary

Working as Senior Software Engineer at Yucca IT Solutions by Scalian Group with 6+ Years of experience.

Specialist in making Home Automation Projects, security devices, PCB design with EasyEDA Tool, iPaaS Tools, Research and development in different IoT Projects.

Specialized in Workato Automation Tool to automate business workflows to make work easy for the customers as per requirements with different connectors, custom connectors, coding connectors as well, CICD, PDF Files, etc.,

CICD Deployment using GitHub Actions directly from one environment to another Workato environment with approval status.

Good Exposure on designing chatbots with Rasa Framework to integrate with Workato, to access Workato platform directly from chatbot without accessing.

Good Exposure to the Apigee-X API Management Tool, integrating with Boomi, Workato, Node APIs, Local URLs, etc.,

Dealing with MicroControllers and MicroProcessors with chip-based & development boards like ESP32 Chip, ESP8266 Chip, ESP-01 Chips, and Raspberry Pi Zero, Pi 3, and Pi 4.

Familiar with Node-Red - building flows and custom dashboards as per requirement for IoT Devices.

IoT data integration with different iPaaS Tools with fewer coding efforts.

Experience

Yucca Scalian Group (Yucca IT Solutions)
Sr. Software Engineer
August 2024 - Present (11 months)
Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

EasyStepIn

5 years 11 months

Senior Integration & Automation Engineer January 2024 - Present (1 year 6 months)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Cognitive IoT Developer
August 2019 - Present (5 years 11 months)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Automation Engineer September 2019 - January 2024 (4 years 5 months)

Bangalore Urban, Karnataka, India

Education

Sree Vidyanikethan Engineering College

B.Tech, Electrical and Electronics Engineering (2014 - 2017)

Loyola Polytechnic College(YSRR) Pulivendula
High School Diploma, Electrical and Electronics Engineering (2011 - 2014)

Aditya High School 10th Class, 10th Class · (2010 - 2011)